UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 23-25 Publications
1998-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/024 PUBS
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Records, publications.
6766110
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 12, 2015
Scope and Contents
Some of the publications are in Chinese and Spanish.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/024: UNITE Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 MB: UNITE Local 23-25 Memorabilia
Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.)--Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.)--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6766110
- 1995 July and October Vol. 44, No. 3-4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: UNITE Local 23-25
    Notes: v.44:no.4 (1995:October)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English; Spanish.
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.4 (1995:October). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.4 (1995:October). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: UNITE Local 23- 25
    Notes: v.44:no.4 (1995:October). Copy 4.
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.3 (1995:July)
  - Item 6: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.44:no.3 (1995:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Local 23-25 News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Language: Chinese.
- 1990 January Vol. 45, No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1996:January)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1996:January). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1996:January). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.45:no.1 (1996:January). Copy 4.
- 1996 January Vol. 45, No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1996 April Vol. 45, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.45:no.2 (1996:April)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.45:no.2 (1996:April). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.45:no.2 (1996:April). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.45:no.2 (1996:April). Copy 4.
- 1996 April Vol. 43 No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1996 August Vol. 45 No. 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.3 (1996:August)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.3 (1996:August). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.45:no.3 (1995:Aug.). Copy 3.
- 1996 August Vol. 45, No. 3 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.45:no.3 (1995:Aug.). Copy 2.
- 1996 October Vol. 45, No. 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1996:October)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1996:October). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1996:October). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1995:Oct.). Copy 4.
- 1996 October V. 45; No. 4 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.45:no.4 (1995:Oct.). Copy 2.
- 1997 Vol. 46 No. 1 January, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1997:January)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1997:January). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1997:January). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.46:no.1 (1997:January). Copy 4.
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1997 Vo. 46, No. 2 April, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1997:April)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1997:April). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1997:April). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1997:April). Copy 4.
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.46:no.2 (1997:Apr.)
- 1997 Vol. 46 No. 3 July, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1997:July)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1997:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1997:July). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.46:no.3 (1997:July). Copy 4.
  - Item 5: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1997 Vol. 46 No. 4 October, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1997:October)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1997:October). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1997:October). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1997:October). Copy 4.
- 1997 Vol. 46 No. 4 October (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.46:no.4 (1997:Oct.). Copy 4.
- 1998 January Vol. 47, No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1998:January)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1998:January). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1998:January). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: v.47:no.1 (1998:January). Copy 4.
- 1998 January Vol. 47, No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 1998 April Vol. 47, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: v.47:no.2 (1998:April)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: v.47:no.2 (1998:April). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: v.47:no.2 (1998:April). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: v.47:no.2 (1998:April). Copy 4.
- 1998 April Vol. 47, No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 1998 July Vol. 47, No. 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: v.47:no.3 (1998:July)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: v.47:no.3 (1998:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: v.47:no.3 (1998:July). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: v.47:no.3 (1998:July). Copy 4.
- 1998 July Vol. 47, No. 3 Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 1998 October Vol. 47, No. 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1998:October)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1998:October). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1998:October). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.47:no.4 (1998:October). Copy 4.
- 1998 October Vol. 47 No. 4 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 1999 January Vol. 48, No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1999:January)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1999:January). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1999:January). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.48:no.1 (1999:January). Copy 4.
- 1999 January Vol. 48 No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 1999 April Vol. 48, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.48:no.2 (1999:April)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.48:no.2 (1999:April). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.48:no.2 (1999:April). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.48:no.2 (1999:April). Copy 4.
- 1999 April, Vol. 48, No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 1999 July Vol. 48, No. 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.48:no.3 (1999:July)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.48:no.3 (1999:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.48:no.3 (1999:July). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.48:no.3 (1999:July). Copy 4.
- 1999 July Vol. 48, No. 3 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 1999 Autumn Vol. 48, No. 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.48:no.4 (1999:Autumn)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.48:no.4 (1999:Autumn). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.48:no.4 (1999:Autumn). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: v.48:no.4 (1999:Autumn). Copy 4.
- 1999 Autumn Vol. 48 No. 4 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 2000 Winter/spring Vol. 49, No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (2000:Winter/Spring)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (2000:Winter/Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (2000:Winter/Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Notes: v.49:no.1 (2000:Winter/Spring). Copy 4.
- 2000 Winter/Spring Vol. 49, No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
- 2000 Spring/Summer Vol. 49, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.49:no.2 (2000:Spring/Summer)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.49:no.2 (2000:Spring/Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.49:no.2 (2000:Spring/Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: v.49:no.2 (2000:Spring/Summer). Copy 4.
- 2000 Spring/Summer Vol. 49, No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
- 2000 Autumn/Winter Vol. 49 No. 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.49:no.3 (2000:Autumn/Winter)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.49:no.3 (2000:Autumn/Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.49:no.3 (2000:Autumn/Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Notes: v.49:no.3 (2000:Autumn/Winter). Copy 4.
- 2000 Autumn/Winter Vol. 49, No. 3 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
- 2001 Winter Vol. 50, No. 1, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (2001:Winter)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (2001:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (2001:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Notes: v.50:no.1 (2001:Winter). Copy 4.
- 2001 Winter Vol. 50 No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- 2001 Summer Vol. 50, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: v.50:no.2 (2001:Summer)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: v.50:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: v.50:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: v.50:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 4.
- 2001 Summer Vol. 50, No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
- 2001 Autumn/Winter Vol. 50, No. 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: v.50:no.3 (2001:Autumn/Winter)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: v.50:no.3 (2001:Autumn/Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: v.50:no.3 (2001:Autumn/Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Notes: v.50:no.3 (2001:Autumn/Winter). Copy 4.
- 2001 Autumn/Winter Vol. 50, No. 3 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- 2002 Spring Vol. 51, No. 21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (2002:Spring)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: v.51:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 4.
- 2002 Spring Vol. 51, No. 1 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
- 2002 Autumn Vol. 51, No. 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: v.51:no.2 (2002:Autumn)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: v.51:no.2 (2002:Autumn). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: v.51:no.2 (2002:Autumn). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: v.51:no.2 (2002:Autumn). Copy 4.
- 2002 Autumn Vol. 51, No. 2 (Chinese), Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: Local 23-25 News, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
- 2003 Local 23-25 News V. 52 (2005: May) Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Notes: v.52 (2003:May)
- Local 23-25 News V. 52: No. 1 (2003; Spring/Summer English and Spanish, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: v.52:no.1 (2003:Spring/Summer)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: v.52:no.1 (2003:Spring/Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Notes: v.52:no.1 (2003:Spring/Summer). Copy 3.
- Local 23and25 V. 52: Mail (2003: Spring/Summer) Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Local 23-25 News V. 52: No. 7 (2003: Autumn) English and Spanish, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Notes: v.52:no.2 (2003:Autumn)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Notes: v.52:no.2 (2003:Autumn). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Notes: v.52:no.2 (2003:Autumn). Copy 3.
- Local 23-25 News V. 52: No. 2 (2003: Autumn) Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 2: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 3: Local 23-25 News, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
- NY Metro Area Joint Board News Vol: No. 1 (2004: Spring/Summer) English and Spanish, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Author: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2004:Spring/Summer)
  - Item 2: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2004:Spring/Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (2004:Spring/Summer). Copy 3.
- NY Metro Area Joint Board News Vol. No. 1 (2004; Spring/Summer) Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)